indianastrology.co.in 2018-08-30

# Privacy Policy - Indian Astrology

At **[Indian Astrology](http://indianastrology.co.in/)** , we take your privacy very seriously and are aware of our responsibility to protect it. Indian Astrology (http://indianastrology.co.in/) appreciates your readership and support and place a high value on your personal privacy. We respect the sensitivity of the information you provide on our web site and staunchly recognise the importance of protecting this information. In adopting this privacy policy (this “Privacy Policy”), our intent is to balance our legitimate business interests in collecting and using your personal information with your reasonable expectations of privacy. This Privacy Policy may be revised or updated at any time and we encourage you to check back often to ensure that you are familiar with the most recent version and the terms of our Privacy Policy.

Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways:

  1. To personalize your experience  
(your information helps us to better respond to your individual needs)
  2. To improve our website  
(we continually strive to improve our website offerings based on the information and feedback we receive from you)
  3. To improve customer service  
(your information helps us to more effectively respond to your customer service requests and support needs)
  4. To administer a contest, promotion, survey or other site feature

We implement a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your personal information when you enter, submit, or access your personal information.

We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others rights, property, or safety. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.

We let you know what information we collect when you use our website(s) and services, and why. If you need more clarification, contact us.

When you visit this website, our servers automatically record information that your browser sends. These server logs may include information such as your Web request, Internet Protocol address, browser type, browser language and the date and time of your request, which are not personally identifiable.

  * This website does not use cookies.
  * Third-party vendors, including Google, use cookies to serve ads based on a user’s prior visits to this website.
  * Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it and its partners to serve ads to users based on their visit to this website and/or other sites on the Internet.
  * Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the advertising opt-out page at http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html (Alternatively, users may opt out of a third-party vendor’s use of cookies by visiting the Network Advertising Initiative opt-out page at http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp)
  * Third-party ad networks serve ads on this website by directly sending them to visitors  browsers. They automatically receive your IP address when this occurs, and may also be using other technologies such as cookies and Web Beacons to measure the effectiveness of their advertisements and/or to personalize the advertisements.
  * This website has no access to or control over the cookies used by third-party advertisers.

Users should consult the respective privacy policies of these third-party ad networks for more detailed information on their practices as well as for instructions about how to opt-out of certain practices. This website’s privacy policy does not apply to, and it cannot control the activities of, such other advertisers or websites.

If users wish to disable cookies, they may do so through their individual browser options. Detailed information about cookie management with specific Web browsers can be found at their respective websites.

Any information you disclose voluntarily on our comments page or in any properties hosted by Indian Astrology (http://indianastrology.co.in/) becomes public information. Indian Astrology (http://indianastrology.co.in/) advise you to use your discretion in sharing information about yourself on the Internet. All information sharing is optional and done so at your own risk. Be careful and responsible when disclosing personal information online.

We reserve the right to delete any comments including off-topic, “spammy” in nature, abusive, use excessive foul language, or include ad hominem attacks.

Once a comment is made public on the Indian Astrology (http://indianastrology.co.in/), we will not remove it by request. As a user, you are responsible for your own communications and are responsible for the consequences of their posting.

Please don’t engage in personal attacks (on authors, other users or any individual), persistent trolling or mindless abuse. The Indian Astrology (http://indianastrology.co.in/) community should focus on intelligently discussing topics with resourceful and constructive ideas. Hate speech such as racism, sexism and homophobia will not be tolerated. We reserve the right to remove any content that might be found extremely offensive or threatening. Spam and advertising content will be removed. Off-topic comments are subject to removal in order to keep the thread on track.

All comments and other content contributed to Indian Astrology (http://indianastrology.co.in/) shall adhere to the privacy policy, and may be edited or removed at Indian Astrology (http://indianastrology.co.in/)’s discretion if it is deemed to be in violation of this policy.

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page and/or send an email notifying you of any changes, and/or update the Privacy Policy modification date below.
